[ WAVES CRASHING ON SHORE ]
♪ [ GUITAR ] ♪
♪ CHEST TO CHEST ♪
♪ NOSE TO NOSE ♪
♪ PALM TO PALM ♪
♪ WE WERE ALWAYS
JUST THAT CLOSE ♪
♪ WRIST TO WRIST ♪
♪ TOE TO TOE ♪
♪ LIPS THAT FELT JUST LIKE
THE INSIDE OF A ROSE ♪
♪ SO HOW COME
WHEN I REACH OUT MY FINGERS ♪
♪ IT FEELS LIKE
MORE THAN DISTANCE ♪
♪ BETWEEN US ♪
♪ IN THIS
CALIFORNIA KING BED ♪
♪ WE'RE 10,000 MILES APART ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN
CALIFORNIA WISHING ♪
♪ ON THESE STARS ♪
♪ FOR YOUR HEART, FOR ME ♪
♪ MY CALIFORNIA KING ♪
♪ EYE TO EYE ♪
♪ CHEEK TO CHEEK ♪
♪ SIDE BY SIDE ♪
♪ YOU WAS SLEEPING
NEXT TO ME ♪
♪ NEXT TO ME ♪
♪ ARM IN ARM ♪
♪ DUSK TO DAWN ♪
♪ WITH THE CURTAINS DRAWN ♪
♪ AND A LITTLE LAST NIGHT
ON THESE SHEETS ♪
♪ SO HOW COME
WHEN I REACH OUT MY FINGERS ♪
♪ IT SEEMS LIKE
MORE THAN DISTANCE ♪
♪ BETWEEN US ♪
♪ IN THIS
CALIFORNIA KING BED ♪
♪ WE'RE 10,000 MILES APART ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN
CALIFORNIA WISHING ♪
♪ ON THESE STARS ♪
♪ FOR YOUR HEART, FOR ME ♪
♪ MY CALIFORNIA KING ♪
♪ JUST WHEN I FELT
LIKE GIVING UP ON US ♪
♪ YOU TURNED AROUND
AND GAVE ME ONE LAST TOUCH ♪
♪ THAT MADE EVERYTHING
FEEL BETTER ♪
♪ AND EVEN THEN
MY EYES GOT WETTER ♪
♪ SO CONFUSED
WANT TO ASK YOU
IF YOU LOVE ME ♪
♪ BUT I DON'T WANT
TO SEEM SO WEAK ♪
♪ MAYBE I'VE BEEN ♪
♪ CALIFORNIA DREAMING ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY ♪
♪ IN THIS
CALIFORNIA KING BED ♪
♪ WE'RE 10,000 MILES APART ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN
CALIFORNIA WISHING ♪
♪ ON THESE STARS ♪
♪ FOR YOUR HEART, FOR ME ♪
♪ MY CALIFORNIA KING ♪
♪ IN THIS
CALIFORNIA KING BED ♪
♪ WE'RE 10,000 MILES APART ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN
CALIFORNIA WISHING ♪
♪ ON THESE STARS ♪
♪ FOR YOUR HEART, FOR ME ♪
♪ MY CALIFORNIA KING ♪